{"sid": "Q86UPV592YZW_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 344084, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 344084, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 360970]], "time_left_end": "284", "answered_time": 360970, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "284", "question_time_start": 360971, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 371997]], "time_left_end": "273", "answered_time": 371997, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "273", "question_time_start": 371998, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 392247]], "time_left_end": "252", "answered_time": 392247, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "252", "question_time_start": 392247, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 399004]], "time_left_end": "246", "answered_time": 399004, "user_answer": "530", "user_correct": "False", "score": "2"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "246", "question_time_start": 399004, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 407904]], "time_left_end": "237", "answered_time": 407904, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "237", "question_time_start": 407905, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 416830]], "time_left_end": "228", "answered_time": 416830, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "228", "question_time_start": 416830, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 423570]], "time_left_end": "221", "answered_time": 423570, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "221", "question_time_start": 423571, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 428530]], "time_left_end": "216", "answered_time": 428530, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "216", "question_time_start": 428530, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 436811]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 436811, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 436811, "question": "98+34", "correct_answer": 132, "events": [["submit", 442160]], "time_left_end": "202", "answered_time": 442160, "user_answer": "132", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 442160, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "202", "question_time_start": 442160, "question": "9+4+4+14", "correct_answer": 31, "events": [["submit", 448008]], "time_left_end": "197", "answered_time": 448008, "user_answer": "31", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "197", "question_time_start": 448008, "question": "7+16+27", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["submit", 457746]], "time_left_end": "187", "answered_time": 457746, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "187", "question_time_start": 457747, "question": "4+94+17", "correct_answer": 115, "events": [["submit", 463104]], "time_left_end": "181", "answered_time": 463104, "user_answer": "115", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "181", "question_time_start": 463104, "question": "93+24+86+98", "correct_answer": 301, "events": [["submit", 493160]], "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 493160, "user_answer": "301", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 493160, "question": "26+317", "correct_answer": 343, "events": [["submit", 499548]], "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 499548, "user_answer": "343", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 499549, "question": "66+64", "correct_answer": 130, "events": [["submit", 504456]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 504456, "user_answer": "130", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 504456, "question": "94+589", "correct_answer": 683, "events": [["submit", 512687]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 512687, "user_answer": "683", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 512687, "question": "9+58+47", "correct_answer": 114, "events": [["submit", 529744]], "time_left_end": "115", "answered_time": 529744, "user_answer": "114", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "115", "question_time_start": 529745, "question": "9+3+3+76", "correct_answer": 91, "events": [["submit", 536720]], "time_left_end": "108", "answered_time": 536720, "user_answer": "91", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "108", "question_time_start": 536721, "question": "16+93", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 542557]], "time_left_end": "102", "answered_time": 542557, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 542557, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "102", "question_time_start": 542557, "question": "57+144", "correct_answer": 201, "events": [["submit", 548612]], "time_left_end": "96", "answered_time": 548612, "user_answer": "201", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "96", "question_time_start": 548612, "question": "78+17+67+14", "correct_answer": 176, "events": [["submit", 561338]], "time_left_end": "83", "answered_time": 561338, "user_answer": "176", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "83", "question_time_start": 561338, "question": "4+27+27", "correct_answer": 58, "events": [["submit", 566939]], "time_left_end": "78", "answered_time": 566939, "user_answer": "58", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "78", "question_time_start": 566940, "question": "8+86+97", "correct_answer": 191, "events": [["submit", 581290]], "time_left_end": "63", "answered_time": 581290, "user_answer": "191", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "63", "question_time_start": 581291, "question": "7+4+4+28", "correct_answer": 43, "events": [["submit", 590493]], "time_left_end": "54", "answered_time": 590493, "user_answer": "43", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "54", "question_time_start": 590493, "question": "67+146", "correct_answer": 213, "events": [["submit", 601238]], "time_left_end": "43", "answered_time": 601238, "user_answer": "213", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "43", "question_time_start": 601238, "question": "7+7+3+69", "correct_answer": 86, "events": [["submit", 618997]], "time_left_end": "26", "answered_time": 618997, "user_answer": "86", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "26", "question_time_start": 618997, "question": "9+66+67", "correct_answer": 142, "events": [["submit", 635122]], "time_left_end": "9", "answered_time": 635122, "user_answer": "142", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "9", "question_time_start": 635122, "question": "56+23", "correct_answer": 79, "events": [["submit", 639208]], "time_left_end": "5", "answered_time": 639208, "user_answer": "79", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "5", "question_time_start": 639209, "question": "74+83", "correct_answer": 157, "events": [["submit", 643525]], "time_left_end": "1", "answered_time": 643525, "user_answer": "157", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 643525, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "1", "question_time_start": 643525, "question": "6+17+74", "correct_answer": 97, "events": []}}}}}